I'm so sorry. Yeah,
we are late and I think we need 3-4
minutes. Yeah,
we're finishing our previous meeting.
Hello. Nice to meet you.
And I sent in for for all.
Do you have any interesting news?
Nope.
It's right now. No, how about you?
No,
I I I have a lot of news about AI and my
teams.
So which are working with AI tools now
because we are preparing a new format of.
Adoption report for Poston L not only
Poston L managers with a lot of
information and it will be our first step
for business case. Yeah,
because you know everybody.
Asks. OK, it's it is very interesting.
Yeah. What about money happened.
We we will form these report we share
with you this variant of report and maybe
Agent 2.
Yeah,
because we've had no test that we
discussed the post and now ideas about
adoption metrics and metrics for teams
and I hope that I can present it in our
session.
During these weeks gap and and I share,
I will share all these document with you.
OK. I have a question where is Vladimir?
Boba.
Yeah, hi, your question.
Yeah, I had today afternoon.
I also pinged you like any documentation
Yeah.
you have on this one.
How to say let's assume I want to do a
POC on this particular AI stent in my
project, right? How do I do that?
You can.
You can find all the commentation in.
DM Tools GitHub for example,
we have links in in this chat and I will
resend you these info today.
I'm very sorry to this very interesting
S.
and hard day.
We have a lot of communications. Yeah.
Give me a second.
3.
None.
Yeah, I will share.
Thank you.
Maybe maybe some questions about oh, whoa,
you are here. Fantastic.
I'm glad to see you one more time today.
Hi, guys.
Yeah, we are ready.
I hope you start it right. That's cool.
Yeah.
OK, let me try to switch.
Shall we start with our regular question?
How many estimates do we have now on the
team?